******you are considering going into
experimental physics,my door is always open.
如果你们对应用物理有兴趣 随时欢迎
Once again,I'm sorry that the
demonstration didn't quite work out,
再次的抱歉 演示不太成功
but now we know what happens when you accidentally
spill Peach Snapple into a helium neon laser.
但至少我们知道了 氦-氖激光管里
不小心洒了桃味饮料的后果
Short answer is...don't.
明智的做法是...别那么做
And now to tell you about the theoretical
physics department is Dr. Sheldon Cooper.
接下来给你们讲理论物理的是
Sheldon Cooper博士
- Dr. Cooper?
- Forget it.
- Cooper博士?
- 我不来
Excuse me.
不好意思
Sheldon,we both agreed to do this.
Sheldon我们可商量好了的
It's a waste of time.
这是浪费时间
I might as well explain the laws of
thermodynamics to a bunch of labradoodles.
我还不如去给
一群拉布拉多犬讲解热力学理论
If you don't do this,I won't
take you to the comic book store.
要是不配合
不带你去漫画书店哟
Hello.
大家好
Nice work with the laser,by the way.
我说 激光实验做的不错嘛
Looking out at your fresh young faces,
看着你们这些年轻的新鲜面孔
I remember when I too was deciding my
academic future as a lowly graduate student.
不禁想起了 当年还是小研究生时
我也如此决定自己的研究方向
Of course,I was 14.
当然 那时我才14岁
And I'd already achieved more than most of
you could ever hope to,despite my 9:00 bedtime.
即使9点就得睡觉 那时也已小有成就
在座大多数至今望尘莫及
Now,there may be one or
two of you in this room
你们中或许有一两位
who has what it takes to
succeed in theoretical physics.
具备天赋 在理论物理上有所建树
Although,it's more likely that you'll spend
your scientific careers teaching fifth graders
当然啦 各位的科学前程
将更有可能教授五年级学生
how to make papier mache
volcanoes with baking soda lava.
怎样用烘烤苏打粉
来糊个纸火山
Oh,good God.
仁慈的主呀
In short-- any
one who told you
总之-- 要是有人告诉你们
that you would someday be able to make
any significant contribution to physics,
你们有朝一日能对物理做出巨大贡献
played a cruel trick on
you,a cruel trick indeed.
真是忽悠你们
绝对绝对是忽悠惨了
Any questions?
有问题吗?
Of course not.
自然没有了
I weep for the future of science.
真为科学的未来感到悲哀呐
Now if you'll excuse me,the
latest issue of Batman is out.
恕我不奉陪 最新的蝙蝠侠发行了
Come,Leonard.
走吧 Leonard
Laser demonstration's
looking pretty good now,huh?
现在看来 我的激光演示很棒吧?
荣誉出品
翻译: 王泳东 gigigao 八重樱 饭特稀
校对: 欧屁屁
时间轴: 咔肉肉
I love this time of the year.
每年的这个时节 真叫我倾心
The leaves are turning,there's
a bracing chill in the air.
树叶转色
空中的寒意让人神清气爽
Plus there's a whole new crop of female grad
students about to put on just enough winter weight
再加上新来的一群女研究生
准备在冬天稍微给自己"加点料"
to make them needy and vulnerable.
让自己愈发惹人呵护
That's right,honey,have another calzone.
这就对了嘛 宝贝 再吃块馅饼
Daddy can wait.
老爹可以再忍忍
Isn't there a university policy
against dating graduate students?
不是有校规嘛?
不能和研究生约会的
No,if you can talk to
them,you can ask them out.
不是 只要能跟她们搭上话
你可以随便约
Damn,there's always a catch.
要死啊! 总给我下套!
Hey,guys.
好呀 小伙子们
Hey,Leslie.
好 Leslie
So,dumbass,I heard you made a
grad student throw up last night.
大傻冒 听说昨晚你把一研究生折腾吐了
The truth can indeed be a finger down
the throat of those unprepared to hear it.
其实是没准备好听我讲的人
自己用手指抠吐的
But why should I cater
to second-rate minds?
我干吗要去给那些二流智商的人讲课?
Because first-rate
minds call you "dumbass"?
因为智商一流的人 总喊你"傻冒儿"
Oh,yeah?Well...
切 是吗? 嗯...
you're a mean person.
你这个毒舌妇
Excuse me,Dr. Cooper,I'm
Ramona Nowitzki.
打扰下 Cooper博士
我是Ramona Nowitzki
I was at your talk last night.
昨晚我听了你的讲课
I think you're just brilliant.
我觉得你真是天才耶
That is the prevailing opinion.
绝大多数人都这么觉得
Oh,now I'm gonna throw up.
这下我要去吐了
Howard Wolowitz,department
of engineering,
Howard Wolowitz 工程系的
co-designer of the International Space
Station's Liquid Waste Disposal System.
参与设计了
国际空间站液体废物处理系统
Dr. Cooper,I've read
everything you've published.
Cooper博士
我拜读了你发表的全部文章
I especially liked your paper on grand
unification using string-network condensates
特别钟意那篇
从弦网浓缩角度阐述大统一理论
and was wondering how
you determined that
我很好奇 你是怎么确定
three-dimensional string-nets provided a
unified picture of ferrnions and gauge bosons?
3D弦网提供了费密子
和规范玻色子的统一描述?
Amazing,an intelligent labradoodle.
很不错啊! 这拉布拉多真聪明!
Woof.
汪汪
The fact is I'm quite close
to a breakthrough in showing
其实呢 我离研究突破就差一点点
how neutrinos emerge from
a string-net condensate.
就快搞清楚
微中子如何在弦网冷凝物中脱出了
Oh,my God,that would change the way
we view the entire physical universe.
天啦 那将会颠覆
全球对整个物理界的认识
It's what I do.
我就是干这个的
You know,the Pishkin-Wolowitz Liquid Waste
Disposal System is turning a few heads as well.
Pishkin-Wolowitz(两名设计者)
废液处理系统也带来一些冲击
Again,ew.
又来了 恶心
You know,I'd love to hear more about
how you intend to add neutrinos.
我很想听你讲讲
怎样加入微中子
Could we get a cup of coffee sometime?
啥时候去喝杯咖啡吧?
I don't drink coffee.
我从不喝咖啡
I do.I love me a cup of joe.
我喝 我爱喝咖啡了
Well,it doesn't have to be coffee.
不一定非要喝咖啡
How about dinner?
一起晚餐如何?
I do eat dinner.
晚饭我还是要吃的
Great. I know a terrific
little Italian place.
那就好 我知道有家意大利餐厅 超棒
I never eat in strange restaurants.
我从不去陌生的餐厅吃饭
One runs the risk of
non-standard cutlery.
指不定就用那些不标准的餐具了
Excuse me?
啊 什么
Sheldon lives in fear
of the three-tined fork.
Sheldon对三个分叉的叉子有恐惧心理
Three tines is not a fork.
三个分叉的根本不能叫叉子
Three tines is a trident.
那叫三叉戟
Forks are for eating,
叉是用来吃东西的
tridents are for ruling the seven seas.
而三叉戟是用来统治七海的
(海神手中的三叉戟)
What if I brought food to your place?
要不我把吃的带去你那儿?
That would be acceptable.
这倒行
On Mondays,I eat Thai food.
周一我吃泰国餐
Mee krob and chicken sate with
extra peanut sauce from Siam Palace.
脆炸米粉 鸡肉沙爹 加上暹罗宫的花生酱
You got it. I already have your address.
没问题 我有你家的地址
What a nice girl.
多好的姑娘啊
Sheldon,do you have any
idea what just happened?
Sheldon 你到底有没有搞懂刚才怎么回事
Yes. Apparently I'm
getting a free dinner.
当然 显然是有人要请我吃饭
Oh,yeah,no,this thing's
majorly out of order.
不好意思 这东西基本上不能用啦
See? Sorry.
看吧 真不好意思
That's okay. Guess
I'm taking the stairs.
没关系 那我走楼梯咯
Where you going?
你去哪家呢?
Oh,are you here to see Leonard?
是来找Leonard的吧
No,Dr. Cooper.
不是 我找Cooper博士
Dr. Sheldon Cooper?
你说的是Sheldon Cooper博士?
We're having dinner.
我们要共进晚餐
Sheldon Cooper?
你确信是Sheldon Cooper?
Tall,thin, looks a little
like a giant praying mantis?
那个瘦瘦高高 长得像
巨人版螳螂煞星
He is cute,isn't he?
他好帅的哟 是吧
Sheldon Cooper?
真的是Sheldon Cooper?
Hi,Leonard.
你好Lenonand
Hey,Ramona. Come on in.
你好Ramona 快进来
Thanks. Where should I put this?
谢谢 这些东西放哪儿呢
Uh,the kitchen's fine.
放厨房就好了
Hey,what are you doing?
你来有事吗?
I need to see this.
这好戏我不能错过哇
The viewing area's right over there.
观众席在那边
Sheldon,your girl... date...
person... Ramona's here.
Sheldon 你女朋... 约会对...Ramona来了
Oh,hello.
你好啊
Oh,sorry I'm late.
不好意思我迟到了
I just got so caught up reading
the draft of your latest paper.
看到你刚发表的论文草本 看得太入迷了
Did you enjoy the humorous footnote
where I illustrate mirror-symmetry
我对镜象对称性作了一个脚注说明
by likening it to the Flash
playing tennis with himself?
把它比喻成闪电和自己打网球
你体会到其中的幽默了吗?
So funny.
太好笑了
But the idea that you might
be able to incorporate gravity,
不得不提的是 你关于重力组合
可能性的猜想
I have to tell you,I found
it physically exhilarating.
真的是让我实打实地兴奋
My hypotheses tend to have that effect.
我的假设通常都有这种效果
I'm sorry I didn't bring
enough for your friends.
不好意思 我没给你朋友带吃的
I assumed we were going to be alone.
我以为就我们两人
Oh,yeah. No,we were just going.
喔 没错 我们正要--
To watch,right?
准备看戏 不是吗
No,come on,now, we're going out.
快 我们马上就出门了
Oh,come on, we'll be quiet.
别这样嘛 我们不说话成吗
Let's go,let's go.
我们还是走吧 走吧
Okay,you two. Have a nice...
好了 祝你们俩的...随便啦
whatever this is.
开心就是了
Okay,you guys,look, I know
this is none of my business,
你们听好 我清楚这事压根跟我没关系
but I just... I have to
ask-- what's Sheldon's deal?
但是我还是要 忍不住想问
Sheldon的"型"到底是啥?
What do you mean "deal"?
什么"型"啊?
You know,like what's his deal?
就是说 他好哪种型的
Is it girls...?
Guys...? Sock puppets...?
女人 男人 布袋木偶?
Honestly,we've been operating under
the assumption that he has no deal.
说实话 在我们的逻辑中
他根本没有"型"
Come on,everybody has a deal.
别这样说 每个人都有喜欢的型啊
Not Sheldon.
除了Sheldon
Over the years,we've formulated many
theories about how he might reproduce.
多年来 我们一直潜心
试图探究他将如何繁衍后代
I'm an advocate of mitosis.
我主张的是有丝分裂
I'm sorry?
什么?
I believe one day Sheldon will
eat an enormous amount of Thai food
我相信 总有一天 当Sheldon吃到
一定量的泰国菜
and split into two Sheldons.
他就会分裂成两个Sheldon
On the other hand, I think Sheldon
might be the larval form of his species,
另一方面 我在想Sheldon可能
是他这个物种的幼虫状态
and someday he'll spin a cocoon and emerge two
months later with moth wings and an exoskeleton.
有一天他会做茧
不出俩月 就破茧成蝶
Okay,well,thanks for the nightmares.
谢谢你俩给我讲恐怖故事
Hey,do you want to hang out with us?
要不我们一起出去逛逛
What are you guys gonna do?
你们有什么节目
My mom's making a brisket tonight.
我妈妈今晚作了胸肉
The one with the little onions?
那种放了小洋葱的?
Yeah,I'm busy,so... Good night.
不好意思 我很忙 晚安吧
Her loss. Let's go.
不去是她的损失 我们走吧
Brisket party! B-
to-the-R-to-the-I-S-K...
胸肉聚会耶 胸 是胸肉的胸
To-the-E-to-the-T...Ooh...
肉 是胸肉的肉 哦也
Don't.
得了吧
Hey,aren't you having breakfast?
你不吃早餐吗?
Yes.
我吃的
Are you experimenting with
nutritional suppositories again?
你又在捣鼓那些营养栓剂啊?
Not in these pants.
穿这条裤子 不干那活儿
So... how'd it go
with Ramona last night?
话说 你昨天和Ramona玩的咋样
Oh,great. She's smart,insightful
爽歪了 她好聪明 好有见解
and she has a very unique
way of,you know,revering me.
而且用一种十分独特的方式 崇拜我
Here's your spinach mushroom omelet.
这是你的菠菜蘑菇煎蛋卷
Thank you.
谢谢
Did anyone touch it?
有谁碰过这个吗?
Gloves were worn by everyone involved.
每个人手上都带上了手套
I was vigilant.
我一直很小心
Ramona pointed out that I've been wasting
20 minutes a day standing on cafeteria lines.
Ramona跟我说 我每次浪费
20分钟在食堂排队
Time which would be better spent tackling
the great physics problems of our day.
这些时间用来攻克世界级的物理课题
会更好哟
You don't tackle the big issues,Ramona.
哎 我们不是攻克难题 Ramona
You fence with them.
是要和它们周旋
En garde. Riposte.
准备好 杀个回马枪
Touche.
说的好
- Morning.
- Hi,Leslie.
- 早上好
- 你好 Leslie
So,Sheldon, I see you're
organizing your papers
Sheldon 我看到你在为Smithsonian
for the Smithsonian
Museum of Dumbassery.
傻冒儿博物馆赶论文呢
There won't be any room until they get
rid of the permanent Leslie Winkle exhibit.
在撤下Leslie Winkle的永久展览前
那里没有多余的展厅
Oh,good one.
喔 正点
I see you got a grad student
to fight your battles for you.
你居然找了一个研究生替你出头
I'll let you keep
your lunch money today.
今天就饶你一马 省省你的午餐费
Okay,Dr. Cooper is on the
verge of a breakthrough.
Cooper博士马上要取得突破性的进展
If you're going to stay,
如果你想待在这里
you'll have to be respectful and quiet.
你就得乖乖的听他的
Wait for me.
等我~~
So have you worked
out the neutrino issue?
微中子问题解决了吗?
Well,to paraphrase Mozart,
为了诠释莫扎特
all the subatomic particles are there.
所有的次原子微粒都齐备了
I just have to put
them in the right order.
我只需要把他们按顺序排列一下
You're so witty.
你可真机敏呀
Aren't I?
敢说不是
Hey,guys, this package came for...
伙计们 这个包裹是
Dr. Cooper is working.
Cooper博士正在工作
Yes,I'm close to a breakthrough.
没错 我马上要取得惊人的进展了
Ooh,it tickles!
哎呀 痒痒!
Sorry.
真抱歉打扰了
Holy crap on a cracker.
偶的神啊
Hey,Penny.
嗨 Penny
Hi. You probably don't
want to go in there.
你最好不要进去
Why? What are they doing?
为啥 他们搞什么呢?
The only way I could explain it would
be in a therapist's office with dolls.
我只能这么解释
里面是一间摆着洋娃娃的医务室
Hoo-boy.
乖乖隆滴东
Dr. Cooper's working.
Cooper博士正在研究
Yeah,I can see that.
是啊 我长着眼睛看得见
Sheldon,Halonight,
Koothrappali's. You coming?
Sheldon 今天是光环之夜 (Xbox360游戏)
Koothrappali家 你来吗?
Oh,yes,it'sHalonight.
对哦 光环之夜
Let me just dry my tootsies.
等我烘干一下我的小脚趾
You're not going toHalonight.
你不会去光环大战吧
Yes,I am. It's Wednesday.
Wednesday'sHalonight.
我要去啊 今儿是周三 周三是光环之夜
Didn't a great man once say, "Science
demands nothing less than the fervent
有个伟人不是说过 科学需要不仅仅是
"and unconditional dedication
of our entire lives"?
一腔热血 而是无条件的奉献我们的一生
He did.
他是说过
And who was that great man?
那么这个伟人是谁呢
Me.
我
Sorry,Leonard.
不好意思 Leonard
Seriously? You're not coming?
你真的不来吗
You heard her. How can I argue with me?
你听到她说的了 我怎么能跟自己唱反调?
Okay,well,once again,
you guys have a good...
又这样 得 你们俩好好的乐吧
whatever this is.
管你们乐些什么
Dr. Cooper, I have to tell you
your friends are holding you back.
Cooper博士 我必须向你指出
你的朋友在拖你后腿
I prefer to think of it as
"I'm pulling them forward."
我倾向于认为"我在促使他们进步"
Halo night?
光环之夜?
A man with your intellectual gifts doesn't
waste an evening playing video games.
你这样资质的人是不会
浪费一晚上时间玩游戏的
He does on Wednesdays.
星期三就会啊
Not if he wants a Nobel Prize.
如果他想拿诺贝尔奖就不会
He does want that.
他还真想拿!
Does a man with my intellectual
gifts play paintball on weekends?
我这样资质的人会在周末打彩弹吗?
What do you think?
你觉得呢?
Drat.
可恶
Now shall we get back to work?
我们现在该继续干活了吧?
I suppose.
我想是的
Battlestar Galactica comes on tonight.
太空堡垒卡拉狄加今晚上映
I guess I can wait for the DVD.
我想我可以等DVD出来
And then never ever watch it.
到时就算买来也永远不看
* You can be my Yoko Ono  *
* You can follow me wherever I go *
* Be my, be my, be
my Yoko Ono, whoa-oa *
* Now that I'm far away *
* It doesn't seem to
me to be such a pain *
* To have you hanging off my ankle *
* Like some kind of ball and chain *
* You can be my Yoko Ono *
* You can follow me wherever I go *
* You can be my
Yoko Ono Whoa-oa-oa *
* You can follow me wherever I go *
Penny! Penny! Penny!
Sheldon, honey, I've told
you, it's a small apartment.
Sheldon 亲爱的
我都跟你说几回了 房子又不大
You only have to knock one time.
敲一下就够了
Please, please, I don't
have a lot of time.
别唐僧了 我没多少时间
Look, Ramona finally dozed off, and
I need you to help me get rid of her.
听着 Ramona总算打瞌睡了
你得帮我甩了她
Get rid of her how?
甩了她? 怎么个甩法?
I don't know, but apparently
I'm in some kind of relationship,
我不知道 但显然我正处于某种关系中
and you seem to be an
expert at ending them.
而你似乎是终结这类关系的老手
Excuse me?
你说什么?
I see man after man leaving
this apartment never to return.
我看见男人们一个接一个从这儿离开
倒是没见过再回来的
Okay, first of all, it
is not man after man.
好吧 首先澄清一点
并不是一个接一个男人
- Dr. Cooper?
- Hide me.
- Cooper博士?
- 把我藏起来
Hide you?
把你藏起来?
I formally request sanctuary.
我正式要求避难
Why aren't you working?
你为什么没在工作?
she distracted me.
她让我分心了
I told you, Penny, I don't
have time for your nonsense.
Penny 跟你说几遍才明白
我没时间听你胡扯
I have important things to do.
我要事缠身
Oh, man.
噢 不是吧
I know what's going on here.
别以为我不知道怎么回事
Really? Well, then will
you explain it to me?
真的吗? 好 那你来给我解释解释吧
You're in love with Dr. Cooper.
你爱上Cooper博士了
Uh, yeah, no, that's not it.
呃 才不是你说的这样
Don't try to deny it.
别想抵赖
He's a remarkable man,
but you have to let him go.
他是非比寻常之人 可你得懂得放手
Oh, gee, okay.
噢 是吗 放就放呗
I know it's hard, but he's a gift to
the whole world, and we can't be selfish.
我知道这很难 可我们不能这么自私
他是上帝赐给这个世界的礼物
Yeah, he's a gift all right.
是啊 他是个天才倒没错
Sisters?
好姐妹?
Uh, sure. Sisters.
呃 当然 好姐妹
Holy crap on a cracker.
真TMTM见鬼了
Sheldon?
What are you doing?
你在干嘛?
It's Morse code.
打莫尔斯码啊
Why?
干啥?
So we can communicate through the wall.
我们就能隔着墙交流了
We are communicating through the wall.
我们不正在隔墙交流么
Yes, but the communication
is not encrypted.
没错 可我们的交流没有加密啊
I don't know Morse code.
我唔识莫尔斯码
It's very simple. This is A ...
很容易的 这是A...
This is B ... This is C...
这是B... 这是C...
Sheldon, I'm not going to learn
Morse code at 3:00 in the morning!
Sheldon 我才不要在凌晨三点学莫尔斯码!
All right.
那好
Don't come in here, don't come in
here, don't come in here, don't...
别进来 别进来 别进来 别进来...
What's going on?
又发什么神经?
Ramona's sleeping on the couch.
Ramona睡在沙发上呢
I know. When is she going home?
我知道 她几时回家?
Never. That's the problem.
她不回家 这就是问题所在
I need your help.
我需要你的援助
What are you talking about?
你说啥呢?
I'm invoking the Skynet clause
of our friendship agreement.
我要求启用"友谊协约"第一条:"天网"条款
(Skynet:电影中的计算机网络)
That only applies if you need me to help
you destroy an artificial intelligence
那款条约只在一种情况下有效:
你需要我帮你消灭人工智能
you've created that's
taking over the Earth.
你创造了它 它却掌控了地球
Come on! Don't nitpick!
拜托! 别死抠字眼儿!
Good night.
晚安
All right.
好吧
I'm invoking our Body Snatchers clause.
那我要求启用"异形入侵"条约
(Body Snatchers: 好莱坞科幻电影)
The Body Snatchers clause requires
me to help you destroy someone we know
"异形入侵"条款要求我帮助你
消灭我们都认识的人
who's been replaced with an alien pod.
而那个人必须变成了外星虫囊
Yes. She's in the living
room. Go. I'll wait here.
没错 她就在客厅里 走吧
我在这儿等你凯旋
Sheldon, what are you doing out of bed?
Sheldon 你不睡觉在干啥呢?
Now! Do it!
快! 消灭她!
You know you need your sleep in order for your
cognitive processing to perform at optimum levels.
你需要足够的睡眠以保证
认知表现处于适宜的水平
Now come on.
要乖乖的啊
Godzilla clause?
"哥斯拉"条款?
(Godzilla 日本科幻电影)
Not unless she destroys Tokyo.
除非她将东京摧毁
Rats.
扯淡
I've got it!
我成功了!
I finally reconciled the black hole information
paradox with my theory of string-network condensates!
我终于用基于弦网冷凝物的理论
解除了黑洞的信息悖论
It's unbelievable!
It's paradigm-altering.
真是难以置信! 那将改变人们的陈见!
And I could not have
done it without you.
多亏了你 我才得以完成
Oh, please, I just offered
a little encouragement.
噢 不用啦 我只不过给了你些许鼓励
It was a lot more than that.
绝对不止些许鼓励
You helped me work out the masses of all
the fermions and you pumiced my hammer toe.
你帮我解决了大量有关费密子的问题
还替我打磨了我的锤头趾
How can I ever repay you?
我要怎么回报你?
Well, would you consider naming
it the Cooper-Nowitzki Theorem?
嗯... 你会把它命名为
Cooper-Nowitzki定理吗?
Who's Nowitzki?
谁是Nowitzki?
(诺维茨基)
I'm Nowitzki.
我就是Nowitzki
Oh, you want me to share credit?
喔 你要我同你分享荣誉?
Get out!
出-去!
Oh, bite me!
噢 别烦我!
Sisters?
好姐妹?
Excuse me, Dr. Cooper.
打扰一下 Cooper教授
I'm Kathy O'Brien.
我是Kathy O'Brien
I just finished reading your paper
reconciling the black hole information paradox
我刚拜读了你的那篇论文
有关解除黑洞信息悖论的
with your theory of string
- network condensates, and it just took my breath away.
你用了基于弦网冷凝物的理论
真是令人惊叹啊 (让我都喘不过气了)
Maybe when I publish it,
I'll include an inhaler.
也许等它发表的时候
我会考虑多加个喷雾器 (治哮喘的)
Would you possibly have any
time for me to pick your brain?
你会不会正巧有空给我解释解释呢?
Let's see. Today's Thursday.
让我想想 今天是星期四
Thursday nights, I eat
pizza from Giacomo's.
星期四晚上 我吃Giacomo餐厅的匹萨
Sausage, mushrooms, light olives.
要放香肠 蘑菇 还要一点橄榄油
Great. I'll bring it to your
place. I have the address.
太好了 我会买去你家的 我有地址
What a nice girl.
真是个好姑娘
Sheldon, do you see
what just happened here?
Sheldon 你知道刚才怎么回事吗?
Yes, I'm getting a free pizza.
当然 我有免费匹萨吃咯
I'm on a roll.
我好运连连喔!
More pad Thai, please.
再来点泰国菜
Sheldon, you've already
had four servings.
Sheldon 你已经吃了四盒了
You might want to
slow down a bit, buddy.
你该吃慢点 伙计 小心咽着
Just one more bite.
就一小口
Sheldon?
Sheldon, are you okay?
Sheldon 你还好吧?
I'm just so... full.
我太... 饱了
That's it. No more Thai food.
受不鸟了 再不吃泰国菜了
翻译: 王泳东 gigigao 八重樱 饭特稀
校对: 欧屁屁